Agalya Panneerselvam



Professional Summary

Versatile professional with 2 years of experience managing large-scale projects. Lead exercises such as data visualization and data management. Kept the team on track on data and project deadlines on budget. Communicating with management and clients to keep them updated.



Employment History

Analyst-Infranomics Consulting - Chennai

Aug. 2021 - Present

- Developed database for diverse projects, Industries to maintain up-to-date data and analyses market trends
- Worked on alignment of various stakeholders and follow up on various MOM of previous meetings, keeping track of things
- Responsible for managing key projects of cluster Management, timelines of projects, discussion flow and tracker
- Ensuring timely tracking and reporting of key business metric to the Cluster Head
- Analyzing current & past financial data performance, reporting the root cause of outcomes
- Preparing reports based on financial data analysis to Cluster Head
- Perform a wide variety of administrative activates and handling confidential information and business critical assignments
- Conducting in-depth research of sourcing data, operating and analyzing and report finding
- Established KPIs and monitoring tools by analyzing data to assist project team
- Creating monthly and quarterly reports for higher management using data visualization techniques in timely and accurate manner

Deputy Manager, ICICI Bank Ltd- Chennai

Oct 2020 - May 2021

- Maintain CEO/CFO relationships with SMEs to originate business and manage the relationship with the customers by growing the book size
- Gather and finalize project requirements of customers and break them down into business and technology components
- Ability to work hand in hand with multiple stakeholders for multiple projects to facilitate requirement gathering interviews, issue clarifications, review documentation, ensure traceability, sign off
- Ability to design business solutions that are best suited for the customers and wellaligned with ICICI technology frameworks
- Collaborate with other Subject Matter Expert to manage and ensure internal customer requirement
- Ensures that plans, risks, issues, actions, schedules, benefits, and other related project are documented and tracked
- Conduct trainings for teams as required delivering high quality performance

Business Analyst, AnandRathi Investment & Service Chennai

Mar. 2019 – Aug. 2019

- Facilitating design sessions with the implementation team to define the solution strong analytical skills, ability to grasp new concepts quickly and adapt to situations
- Creating, analyzing, and validating detailed functional specifications
- Identifying the current and future state business processes
- Understanding of the software development lifecycle models and methodologies
- Responsible for setting project direction and providing project oversight
- Proven experience in delivering Analytics Solutions
- Good communication/problem solving/analytical bent of mind

Personal info

Phone:

+91 73586 86721

Email:

agalsiva.paner@gmail.com

Address:

1, Rajiv Gandhi Street, New Perungalathur, Chennai 600063 (IN)

Languages

Tamil



English



Telugu



Hindi



Skills

Project Scope, Planning, & Prioritizing | Resource Requirements & Management | Scheduling, Organizing, & Time Management | Project Requirements Gathering & Analysis | Agile and WaterFall, Agile Framework | Oral & Written Communication Skills | Milestone Development & Deliverables Tracking | Team Leadership & Cross-Functional Team Collaboration | Project Budget Planning & Administration | Analytical Thinking, Problem Solving, & Attention to Detail | Microsoft: Project, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access

Certification

Project Management Professional -2019

National University of Singapore, Singapore

Project Management- 2020

ITM Business School, Chennai

Education

ITM Business School, Chennai, Tamil Nadu

PGDM- Post Graduate Diploma in Management, Finance, May. 2020

Bharath University, Chennai, Tamil Nadu

Bachelor of Science, Physics, May. 2018

St.Anne's Matriculation Higher Secondary School, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 12th, Apr. 2015

St.Anne's Matriculation Higher Secondary School, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 10th, Apr. 2013